PABLO CEBOLLADA

RENDER PROGRAMMER

CONTACT

paablooch.github.io

Pablo Cebollada Hernández

<u>PaablooCH</u>

paabloo.ch@gmail.com

+34 655 072 165

Barcelona, Spain

SKILLS

Dynamic worker

Quick learn capability

Critical thinking

Problem-solving

Adaptability and flexibility

Strong work ethic

PROJECTS

Axolotl Engine - Starfall Rebellion

Megaman Game 2D-Plataform

Undercooked 3D-Unity-Puzzle

Deus Ex Machina In-house Engine

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES



C++



C#

OpenGL API



Java.

TOOLS









Unity



PROFILE

I'm a junior programmer, with a strong background in the creation of applications and a passion for graphics programming. My experience includes the development of video games in 2D, with non-commercial engine, and in 3D using Unity, and lately, I have developed the graphics part of an engine for the final master project I coursed, which has allowed me to develop skills using and creating shaders with OpenGL and my understanding and use of the C++ language. I am excited about the opportunity to contribute to your company's success and look forward to discussing how my skills and experience can benefit your team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Render & Engine Programmer (Master's studio)

Horizons Games

January 2023-Present

- I developed a series of features in the rendering system of the engine, involving the use of multiple shaders with different rendering purposes. Additionally, I worked on features for both the engine and gameplay and reviewed code.
- Good Knowledge of C++ and Render technics.
- · Good Knowledge about Life Cycle of Game Development.

Software Developer

IThink UPC

February 2022-February 2023

- Full stack developer, developing web applications for third parties.
- · Collaborating in big teams.
- · Working with a multidisciplinary team.
- · Utilizing the Scrum methodology with Jira to manage projects.
- Ability to effectively communicate with customers.
- Working with the implementation of various programming patterns.

Software Developer (Internship)

Telespazio Ibérica

April 2021-January 2022

- Full stack developer, developing web applications for first party.
- Met all the deadlines set by the client.
- Utilizing the Scrum methodology

EDUCATION

Master in Advanced Programming for AAA Videogames

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - BarcelonaTech - Talent School 2022 - 2023

Degree in Computer Science

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - BarcelonaTech 2017 - 2022

LANGUAGES

HOBBIES

Spanish

Catalan

English

I spend my spare time mostly playing video games, especially shooters and MOBAs, but recently, I've started playing JRPGs like Persona 5, and survival horrors like Signalis. Additionally, I like to read papers about rendering techniques to keep myself updated and I set aside time to practice some sports.